cornerclassifieds.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy - Free Classifieds | CornerClassifieds.com

**Privacy Policy**

 **General**

CornerClassifieds.com (this website) is owned and operated by MEDIASITE S.C. We take your privacy seriously. We utilize safe, secure technology to protect your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the personal information that we collect and receive through our websites. We value your trust in us and will work hard to earn your confidence, so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to family and friends.

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy, will be posted on our websites. You may review a current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of the home page of this website.

 **Information We Collect and How It Is Used**

Like most standard web servers, our websites use log files to collect standard web log entries, including your IP address, page URL, browser type, platform type, and timestamp. We use this information to diagnose problems with our server, for the purposes of system administration, and to otherwise provide you with better services.

We collect personally information such as name, email address and contact phone number while you post ad using our website. Your name or ad owner name is required but other personal information is optional to input. Such information will be displayed when other users view your ad so that they can contact you if they are interested in your products or services. You may put your contact information inside your ad description. However, you understand that ad description and other contact information will be displayed on the website when other users view your ad details, and that our website pages may be linked by third party websites or search engines. You agree that we may send you email using your email address if provided when the users viewing your ad want to contact you by using our email system.

The users of our services may contact you by themselves via your email address and/or phone number if you provided in your posting. MEDIASITE S.C declines all responsibilities for such contact and all results caused by such contact.

If you contact us directly by sending email to an email address listed on Contact Us page, or any email address at our website domain names, or send comments through our website, your email address will be used if we reply to your comments or questions.

Please do not post or submit any personal information that you expect to keep private.

 **Protecting your Privacy**

We do not sell or rent your personal data to anyone. The personal data you provide us is saved in a secure environment and is kept in our records. Information collected is stored in a single, secure database, accessible only by MEDIASITE S.C members. We employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies in order to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information. Because this website is hosted by third party (web hosting provider), we cannot guarantee complete security.

Our websites, or users of our websites, may provide links to third party websites. We are not responsible for, or have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites. We encourage all users to read the privacy policies of all websites visited.

 **Use of Cookies**

Like most standard web servers, our web server may set and access "cookies", small text files placed on your hard drive, to keep track of the pages visited. The "cookies" do not reveal personal information, rather give us statistical data to help analyze our web page flow and measure effectiveness. By tracking the overall traffic patterns of our visitors, we can make the site more responsive to our visitors" needs and interests. Using cookies is popular by many websites.

Third party websites made available by, or through, our websites, may also assign cookies. We do not control the use of cookies by third party websites, have any access to such cookies or to any information that they contain.

 **Compliance with the Law**

We reserve the right to release information about our users in order to comply with the law. We may also release personal data to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our services, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our websites, our users, or the general public.

 **A Special Note about Children**

We does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 18. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use our websites unsupervised. If you are under the age of 18, you may use our websites only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. If we learn that a posting has been submitted by a person under the age of 18 without supervised, we will remove that post.

Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments, please [Contact Us.](http://cornerclassifieds.com/index.php?page=contact)

CornerClassifieds.com  
Owned and Operated by MEDIASITE S.C
